# **Hady Mohamed Mohamed**

## Front-end Developer

- +201012315216
- hady812012@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/hady812012
- Faisal -Algiza

#### **OBJECTIVES**

Web developer with 5 years of experience. I worked in several companies and also worked as a freelancer. I acquired many skills and created a large number of successful websites and systems.

I seeking to obtain a job opportunity that is commensurate with my experience, to develop more than my skills, benefit the company, and build relationships with customers by understanding their needs and working to translate them into reality.

#### **TECHNICAL & SOFT SKILLS**

HTML \CSS \JS \SASS \TS WordPress Communication \Teamwork

Angular Nodejs \Reactjs (Basic) Problem-solving \Adaptability

PrimeNG \Tailwindcss Organisational skills

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### 8X CRM

Front-end developer Jul 2022 - Present

- At first, I worked on the Custom Application, especially the Multi-Page Application, and after that the company started working on the Single Page Application, especially Angular Framework.
- The company is specialized in CRM and they made a decision to renew it using Angular, and I was responsible for this renewal in cooperation with the team.

Gallop Media Nov 2021 - Jul 2022

## Front-end developer

The company's specialty was in digital marketing, as the company managed all aspects of the client's media, and I worked as a front-end developer, especially in the multi-page application, and assisted the Laravel developer to implement the entire site.

CreMedia Eq Mar 2020 - Nov 2021

# Front-end developer

At this time, I was working as a WordPress developer, but I started working on a small custom application for some clients.

CodeStan Jan 2019 - Mar 2020

# WordPress developer

I worked as a WordPress developer during this period, The template that is compatible with the client's requirements is selected and modifications are made to it to be suitable for his field.

## **EDUCATION & LANGUAGES**

Bachelor of Commerce 2018

Majors: Accounting Cairo University

# **LANGUAGES**

English Very good

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Angular - The Complete Guide

with Maximilian Schwarzmüller Udemy

The Complete JavaScript Course

with <u>Jonas Schmedtmann</u> Udemy

Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More: The

**Complete Bootcamp** 

with <u>Jonas Schmedtmann</u> Udemy

Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More: The

**Complete Bootcamp** 

with Kevin Powell YouTube

Front-end Diploma

Mesmak